Guide to the Kilpatrick Collection of Cherokee Manuscripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Notebook #13: "Uwedasati No. 22, 19, 20 1940-1964"
  - Recto: Unidentified note; Verso: List of names, 1882 (Box 22, Folder 1829)
  - Obituary, Names and death dates 1950-1952, circa 1952 (Box 22, Folder 1830)
  - Financial record, undated (Box 22, Folder 1831)
  - Recto: Sears invoice; Verso: Short text, "tsadudalesdi nigesvna", unated (Box 22, Folder 1832)
  - List of names, undated (Box 22, Folder 1833)
  - Hymn, undated (Box 22, Folder 1834)
  - Letter to Squirrel Sequichi, 1947 January 14 (Box 22, Folder 1835)
    Translated in Shadow, pp. 100-101
  - Financial record, undated (Box 22, Folder 1836)
  - Duncan, Walter. Letter to Dollie Duncan on Oklahoma State Penitentiary stationary, circa 1950 (Box 22, Folder 1837)
  - Duncan, Walter. Letter to Dollie Duncan on Oklahoma State Penitentiary stationary, circa 1950 (Box 22, Folder 1838)
  - Duncan, Walter. Letter to Dollie Duncan on Oklahoma State Penitentiary stationary, circa 1950 (Box 22, Folder 1839)
  - Duncan, Walter. Letter to Dollie Duncan on Oklahoma State Penitentiary stationary, circa 1950 (Box 22, Folder 1840)
  - Duncan, Walter. Letter to Dollie Duncan on Oklahoma State Penitentiary stationary, circa 1950 (Box 22, Folder 1841)
  - Duncan, Walter. Letter to Dollie Duncan on Oklahoma State Penitentiary stationary, circa 1950 (Box 22, Folder 1842)
  - Duncan, Walter. Letter to Dollie Duncan on Oklahoma State Penitentiary stationary, circa 1950 (Box 22, Folder 1843)
  - Duncan, Walter. Letter to Dollie Duncan on Oklahoma State Penitentiary stationary, 1951 February 7 (Box 22, Folder 1844)
  - Letter, undated (Box 22, Folder 1845)
    page 2 of a letter, page 1 not included
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 22, Folder 1846)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 22, Folder 1847)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 22, Folder 1848)
  - Medical formula in English, undated (Box 23, Folder 1849)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1850)
  - Recto: Letter in English to Mr. Proctor about land rental; Verso: Medical formula, 1940 December 14 (Box 23, Folder 1851)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1852)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1853)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1854)
  - Medical formula in English, undated (Box 23, Folder 1855)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1856)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1857)
  - Medical formula and with musical notation in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, undated (Box 23, Folder 1858)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1859)
  - Community or administrative records, circa 1939 (Box 23, Folder 1860)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1861)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1862)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1863)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1864)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1865)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1866)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1867)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: English writing practice, undated (Box 23, Folder 1868)
  - Saloli Eladi Usgo. Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1869)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Saloli Eldai Usgo Coll. (taken down from dictation, Saloli's widow by Sigwanida, Oct. 1963)"
  - Nedi Atsadi (Fisheman, Ned). Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1870)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Nedi Atsadi Coll. (taken down from dictation of Nedi's son by Sigwanida, Oct. 1963)"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1871)
    Note on page in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Nancy Hogner, Aug. 4, 1966"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 23, Folder 1872)
  - Typewritten text in English related to Fraulein von Bulow, undated (Box 23, Folder 1873)
  - Letter: Welling, Oklahoma, 1947 March 15 (Box 23, Folder 1874)
  - Recto: unidentified text; Verso: form bill from United Sew-Vac center, McKinney, Texas, to Mrs. Minnie Jumper in Welling, Oklahoma, undated (Box 23, Folder 1875)
  - Medical formula for a burn, 1963 August 16 (Box 23, Folder 1876)